Oh hello friends, namaste,
you all are heartily welcome to the investing process,
friends, in this video we will talk about
some important stocks,
we will cover some important news related to them
in detail, so if
you guys have any of these stocks at any level,
then this video is going to be very important for you,
so first of all we will talk about
Jubilant Food Limited, so
today in Jubilant Food Limited we got to
see a good rise in the stock, it will be
around 1%, so Jubilant Food
Limited has come out with some great positive news today,
if we talk about the first news out of that, then Jubilant Food
Limited has announced that in the coming
2020, that is, in the financial year 2024, the
company will give you approximately 750
Domino's Pizzas and also 35 Pops,
you used to open restaurant companies, they will get this share
in the financial year 2014,
so obviously how is this news, then
obviously the company is expanding its business  They are
continuously investing in their business,
so
obviously this is positive news for the long term.
So this is panel
news. If we talk about other news,
then the second news is friends, not the share
pattern. I tell you again and again that
if you invest in any company on your own, then
you should not only study the quarterly basis
number but also the
rolling pattern which is updated from quarter to quarter.
You should also know how to study those things in detail.
If you are investing in the market on your own, then
friends, the
rolling pattern is also
considered a very important parameter.
So if we talk about the share pattern of Jubilant Foods Limited
this time, then first of all,
if we talk about Pramod Rakhi, the
promoter, you must be seeing that
he had
around 41.94%, which is fine,
he has had this much stake for a long time. So, if
he has made any change now, then it is
not at all like that. We saw the promoter holding the
same amount, around 42%,
but the good thing is that it is very good, which is very
good.  You can definitely consider this point as very positive
and that is
friends please, first of all the data which the company had
in the last June quarter, in the June quarter a year ago, the
share of the company which was with the
other person was around 1.84%,
after that gradually the share of the company has come
down to
around
0.63% from the day before yesterday, so what kind of news is this, I mean what kind of
news is this, obviously this is very great news,
please first of all the data, the more it is, the
more it is for the company, that is, it is a
very risky point for the company, the
more it will decrease, it will be
very great for the company, that is, if
you just do this then this is very great positive
news, so obviously the company is getting more shares than the
holdings it had, the
best thing is that
whatever shares the company had,
they had kept them with the other person, which is
almost
doing so, which you
can definitely consider as a great positive,
700, if you want, you can study some other points also,
like the
matter of FC in Sharoni pattern  If we talk about it, then it is continuously
decreasing its stock, which if we
talk about this time also, then
they decreased a little bit this time also, along with this, the
good thing is that look, there are S
and F, there is competition going on between them,
sometimes they will buy shares and sometimes they will buy shares,
this thing keeps going on, you have seen that
FC is continuously going from goods to B, but
in comparison to that, whatever goods, whatever shares
FC is sending, friends, we
also used to get good consistency, at
one time it was 17%, which is now
around 22%, if we see more of this data, then
obviously if we
talk about the growth pattern of Jubilant Food Limited, then
we get to see a decent growth rolling pattern,
so no doubt, these two
news which we got earlier, the company is
expanding its business in a great way,
opening new stores,
which will give
long term growth to the company, this is very good news,
secondly, the company had taken loan to increase its sales
Please keep it with the other person, that too slowly,
they are getting their biodata by reducing their health to the other person,
which is a
very good data. If we talk about the
company Jubilant Foods and Criminal, the
company is very good friends, it is a very good
company, a very big international money company
and it has two very popular brands, you
know one is Domino's Pizza and the other is
Donkey Dona and
in Domino's Pizza, about 70% of the company's profit is
old, let's say even now if you look at it,
you will see 60 plus from their market
in the domestic market, so
note out, it is a very good company, a leading
company in its sector, if we talk about the profit of the last one
year, then it does
not show any special profit, there is a decline of around 720%, if we
talk about five years, some special
properties have not been given in it yet,
if we talk about this top, then the company is
not bad, but
you will get to see this stock which has a lot of questions,
if you look at its maximum then
you will understand it easily.  Since 2010, we get to
see its listing and it
is a stock with a lot of option nose,
meaning it is a stock with a lot of wallet potential,
but the company is very
good for growing the company and in the long term, if someone
bought it at the top, now even if you just hold and sit, the
company is very good, in the coming time, it will
definitely give you great returns even from this level,
so please do
not sell at a loss, whatever quantity you have, you just have to
hold and sit, it will give you this return
comfortably, if someone has to
take this type of decision, then
look at the company's numbers on 25th July, next week,
after that you will get the best clarity,
should you go now after looking at these numbers
or wait for a few more days, then
look at the numbers, after that you
can take your decision, the next top is
our Deepak Nitrite Limited, so
talking about Deepak Nitrite, today
we got to see a little bit of positive news,
but you saw that the
great fall shown in the previous stock, you will still
see it, even after coming down by almost 20%, it is
around 11 100 11  And this stock has
fallen with consistency and more important than that,
we used to trade the stock below its whole number, which means that as
long as these stocks
trade below 2000, then we get to see a weakness being
indicated by this
and these stocks, by the way, you got to see the count
in the last month, only in this stock,
friends, in all the chemical stocks,
we
saw very minimal pressure from the last month
and the reason behind it is that the
markets are already running badly,
we get to see the exports of this company in the global country, so in that, there is a
very slow down in the global country, due to which the
markets are running poorly,
that you will see the numbers of these chemical companies
this time too or even till the quarter on this cotton, you can
see their numbers bad,
due to which there will be
a good profit booking in the stock before the numbers come, so
how come the numbers are already running low, if
their numbers will be bad then the market will be
worse than the current trend, so
this is very important to see  It is going to be interesting
but if we talk about the company then today
a very good news has come out
which is about the shares and holding pattern of the company
and on this matter the share pattern of Limited is going to be
very important because
last time suddenly that is simply the promoter bought
3 1/2% stake in his company and
after that you saw that they are getting great
orders because
this time also the promoter made any changes or changes
so it is not like that at all,
we are seeing the same amount of stock as they had in the previous photo,
which you
can definitely consider it a pause report,
if we talk about FSC then they were continuously selling,
this time we have
seen more in reverse order
which they
increased a little, talk about the stock which was being
bought continuously, friends this time also
you used to
increase almost, if we talk about the public
which from last year at one time
you were at 35.5, after that 34 33, after that
below 31 28 and this time friends  The
stock is down from 28 to 27, which means
we are continuously getting public holdings in the stock and the
reason behind this is that
before this data was made at the top of 3000, the public bought the stock in a very impressive manner
as if the stock is down
and the stock is moving from 2021 to
2023, which means it has been a dead year, the
stock has not made any returns for a dead year, which
means it has not even achieved its old level,
so you know that when any stock
falls, there is no momentum seen after that, so the
public who bought at the top slowly
start selling at a loss,
friends,
you must be seeing this data of such stocks now slowly the
public is continuously selling such companies in the middle at a loss
and they are getting out, so
I would like to say that till now
if you have made a profit in the stock, then it is a great company
if you have it, you can also do it by averaging
because the company's business model, the
management of the company is excellent, along with the clients of the company
and the history of the company is also available, so
before this such a multiplier fall  This has happened
before, this company has
faced such slow downs many times, so
please, the company does not end due to this, in the
long run, you will get to see the journey of this company only above,
yes, still if you want to buy someone,
you have not done it yet, then I
think you should see the company's numbers on August 3, only
after that if you take your
decision, then I think
you will get the best clarity for you,
after that even if you have to buy the stock by paying 100-200 rupees, it will be the
best decision for you
because after hitting 62, the numbers of this company will be
bad, but how much is it doing,
if the
company shows worse numbers than the market, then
obviously there can be more decline in the stock
and the stock can again reach 1750, so
therefore, if you buy the stock by giving the numbers on August 3, then it will be the
best clarity for you, but
whatever the numbers are, if you have bought the
stock for the long term, then you can close your eyes and
continue the stroke,
next topic is our SO LDS SO
All we had to see about LDS was that on the last day we
saw the company's numbers. The
company's numbers came after 3:30, so what is
Badar's reaction to it, initially there was a slight
decline but overall,
this number has been appreciated by the people,
so how are the company's numbers, friends, if we
talk about the numbers, the consistency
shown by its numbers, then this time also the company was
seen maintaining its numbers, so the stock has achieved the
level of thousand, which is a
very big whole number, so will it be able to sustain and
show a rally, this is also going to be very
interesting to see because if you
look at the nature of the stock, then the stock is
now seen moving in a similar manner, once there was a great
rise, then one or two one and a half years of consolidation,
after that another 310 won, then a decline,
then it has been almost a year, the stock was at the
4000 level in the same consultation, so it has broken
because it will be able to show the journey ahead, so
this is also going to be very interesting to see,
if the journey is not shown then please give it a
good company's share in the last, this is also a good company's share
You will definitely get to see it being made one more time after breaking it in the
morning. If you have any
doubt, comment.